Ho Long Ting

Mobile: 62580284

Email: longtingho2010@gmail.com



CALVIN HO



MY PORFOLIO

Introduction

I graduated from a front-end development bootcamp where I gained skills in **React**, **HTML**, **CSS**, and **JavaScript**. I am passionate about creating visually appealing and functional web pages that provide a good user experience. I am a quick learner and resilient person that could continuous improvement and growth in my skills and knowledge.

Front-end Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React
- Git & Github

EDUCATION

2023 MARCH-JUNE

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER PROGRAM COHOERT 7

CLAP@JC X GERERATION

- Build up technical skills in web development like HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT
- Provide experience to create visually appealing and functional web pages

2020- 2022 BACHELOR OF SOCIAL SCIENCES (HONOURS) IN MEDIA AND SOCIAL COMMUNICATION

HONG KONG BAPTIST UNIVERSITY

• CGPA: 3.24/4

2017-2019

HIGHER DIPLOMA IN SPORTS ADMINISTRATION

HONG KONG INSTITUTE OF VOCATIONAL EDUCATION (CHAI WAN)

• CGPA: 2.69/4

EXPERIENCES

2019/08-2022/04 ROUND PRODUCTION

Event Promoter (Part-Time)

- Handling with customer's complaints
- Answering customers' enquiries and dealing with customers' requests
- · Handling with any emergencies

2020/01-2021/01 FIVE TO ONE CAFE
Waiter (Part-Time)

- Providing excellent customer service to guests
- Offering menu recommendations upon request

Expected Salary: Negotiable

SKILLS

- PROFICIENT IN MICROSOFT WORD, POWERPOINT, AND EXCEL
- PROFICIENT IN ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR, PHOTOSHOP, AND PREMIERE PRO
- QUICK CHINESE AND ENGLISH INPUT METHOD
- FLUENT IN CANTONESE, ENGLISH AND MANDARIN